Selim Maurice Franklin papers, 1873-1931
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Zeckendorf Family Papers, 1887-1911
  - Hugo A. Zeckendorf Jewelry Co.: Cash Book. August 1898-June 1899 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Hugo A. Zeckendorf Jewelry Co.: Bills. 1898-1899 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Hugo A. Zeckendorf Jewelry Co.: Miscellaneous financial records including a Ledger Book. 1896-1899 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Series V: William Herring Papers, 1882-1911
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Leases, deeds, agreements. 1900-1905 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Bisbee Flume Papers. 1904 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Transfer of pipeline to Bisbee-Naco Water Co. 1904 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - W. H. Hatcher vs. Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co. 1905 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Suit against Territorial Board of Equalization of the Territory of Arizona. 1905-1906 (Box 78, Folder 5-7)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Various legal cases. 1899-1903 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    Includes suits involving:
    M. B. Morse
    B. Carretto
    James Brogan
    G. H. French
    E. G. Ord
    Chochise County Tax Collector
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Rock Creek Lumber Agreements. 1890-1893 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Miscellaneous material. (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Correspondence with the Modoc Group, New Mexico. 1902-1904 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Legal Papers of the Modoc Group, New Mexico. 1888-1904 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Modoc Group notes, maps, etc. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Delevin, Alice and Copper Bottom Claims. 1903-1905 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Black Jack Claim. 1901-1905 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Brother Jonathan Claim. 1906 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Cuba Claim. 1904-1906 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Macomb Claim. 1904-1906 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Midget Claim. 1904-1906 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Phelps Claim. 1905-1906 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Catalina Lode Claim. 1904-1905 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Fairview Lode Claim. 1890, 1902-1905 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Havana Lode Claim. 1904-1905 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Jamaica Lode Claim. 1900-1902 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Manila Lode Claim. 1904-1905 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Copper Queen Consolidated Mining Co.: Tutuila Lode Claim. 1905 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Detroit Copper Mining Co.: Suit against the Board of Equalization, Graham County, Arizona Territory. 1898-1900 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Detroit Copper Mining Co.: Territory of Arizona vs. Rodriques and Posada. 1898 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Hagan & Matthias vs. Detroit Copper Mining Co. 1899 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Detroit Copper Mining Co.: Suit against M. Avila, et al regarding then Morenci miners strike. 1903 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Detroit Copper Mining Co.: Miscellaneous papers. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Planches de Plata Mining Group, Sonora Mexico: Seiberling vs. Bornio. 1898 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Ivan Hoefeld vs. Detroit Copper Mining Co. 1908 (Box 80)
    Reporter's Transcript of Evidence in the above case heard in the District Court, First Judicial District of the Territory of Arizona, in and for the County of Pima.
  - Arizona and Boston Copper Mining Co.: Various papers including the suit of J. F. Reynolds. 1899-1900 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Golden Rule Copper Co.: Various papers. 1900-1901 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Indiana-Arizona Group of Mines: Miscellaneous papers relating chiefly to the Paddy Woods Claim. 1908-1910 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - E. Woods, et al vs. Indiana-Arizona Development Co. 1908-1910 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Mary E. Cribb vs. Indiana-Arizona Development Co. 1909-1910 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Mary E. Cribb vs. H. C. Sheridan, et al. 1909-1910 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Tombstone Mill and Mining Co.: Correspondence chiefly with W. J. Cheyney. 1898 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Tombstone Mill and Mining Co.: Legal case with the Empire Mining and Milling Co. 1897-1898 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Tombstone Mill and Mining Co.: Various legal papers and notes. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Lucky Tiger Combination Gold Mining Co.: Various cases. 1905 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Bonanza and Red Top Mines. 1892-1911? (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - San Carlos Mining Co.: Correspondence. July 1901-March 1906 (Box 82, Folder 2-3)
  - Mine Taxes: Correspondence, miscellaneous material. 1905 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Mine Taxes: County Tax Assessment. 1905 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Mine Taxes: Legal papers. 1905 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Mine Taxes: Territory of Arizona vs. Board of Supervisors of Graham County, Arizona. 1905 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Mine Taxes: Territory of Arizona vs. Board of Supervisors of Yavapai County, Arizona. 1905 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Proposed Tax on Bullion: Correspondence, etc. 1906-1907 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Bear Creek Mining Company. 1903 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - "Boston Group" of Mines. 1901 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Copper Crown Mine. 1885-1886 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Cougar Mine. 1892-1894 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Hawk-Eye Mine (Abstract of Title). (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Little Wonder Mine (Abstract of Title). (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Long Shorty Mining Claim. 1899 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Poor man and Cyclone Mining Claims. 1904 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Santa Rosa Mining Company. 1904 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Vizina Consolidated Mining Company. 1882-1888 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - George E. Fitzgerald vs. Dragoon Mining Company. 1899 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Richard Coulter and the South Bisbee Copper Mining and Townsite Improvement Company (Hardscrabble Mine). 1899?-1904 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Mining claims in the Reed Mining District, Pima County. 1903 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Narrow Gauge Railway, regarding bond issue in Pima County. 1904 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co.: Assessment, returns, etc. 1902-1904 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Sarah A. Graham vs. El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co. 1900-1905 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Wolf & Woods vs. El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co. 1901-1904 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co. vs. G. Meyers& G. Richards. 1904-1905 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co. vs. W. B. Bond regarding Rodeo Condemnation. 1901-1904 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co.: Correspondence regarding Rodeo station, New Mexico. 1903-1904 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co.: Rodeo station maps. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - El Paso and Southwestern Railroad Co.: Miscellaneous legal papers, etc. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous railroad papers. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Estate: Bacon, Henry D. 1893-1899 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Estate: Bacon, Julia A. 1899-1900 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Estate: Murray, P. J. 1900 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Estate: Ross, Daniel D. 1898-1902 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Estate: Ross, Daniel D. suit against Mutual Life Insurance Co. of New York. 1897-1899 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Estate: Taylor, William B. 1896-1900 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Estate: Woods, William P. 1896-1908 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Estate: Blinn, Marshall. 1886-1887 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Estate: Castenada, Jose M. 1884-1903 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Estate: Deck, John. 1905 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Estate: Wildman, Machomich. 1905 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Estate: Wright, Frank M. 1905 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Estate: Zabriskie, Adelaide S. 1901-1907 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Legislative Documents (Territorial and Federal). (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Erie Cattle Co. 1894-1899 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - J. B. Breathitt vs. Eduardo de la Cuesta. 1900-1901 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Clay Manufacturing Co.: Bankruptcy, etc. 1901-1904 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
  - Arizona Clay Manufacturing Co.: Miscellaneous financial records, notes. (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth & W. W. Williams vs. W. S. Edwards. 1902-1910 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Lillie Goldtree Property in Tucson, Arizona. 1899 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - S. L. Pomeroy vs. M. Martinez. 1891 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - John McGowan vs. Wiley E. Jones. 1899 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - H. S. Bradford vs. American Wolfram Co. 1900 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Probate of will of James Schley. 1901 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - M Denn, et al vs. South Bisbee Copper Mining Townsite Improvement Co. 1903 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Burns & Thomas H. Collins agreements regarding oil lands. 1904 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Helen S. Meade vs. W. K. Meade (Divorce). 1906-1907 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - U. S. Patent for an Air Brake System, The Richards & O'Malley Co. 1907 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - D. F. Garretson vs. Pacific Crude Oil Company. No date (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Buckeye Canal Company: various notes. (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Tobias Oberfelder, Max Oberfelder and J. G. Bothin: Articles of Agreement made and entered into on this day of September A. D. 1884 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Life Membership Card in Lodge No. 385, B. P. O. Elks. (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - "Resolution of Condolence" from the Elks on the death of Mrs. Herring. May 18, 1903 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Specifications for an addition to personal residence on Main Street, Tucson, prepared by J. H. Holmes, architect. No date (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Safe Account. 1893-1895 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Safe Account. 1896 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Railroad Register. September 1, 1903 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Mining Register. September 1, 1903 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Cash Book. September 1898-June 1901 (Box 86)
  - Cash Book. January 1899-September 1907 (Box 86)
  - William Herring Docket Book. 1882-1887 (Volume 87)
  - William Herring Docket Book. 1898-1908 (Volume 88)